Experience of the Awakening of the Kundalini Energy
Doświadczenie obudzenia Energii Kundalini
Guided by Shri Mataji Nirmala Devi 1987-0505, Australia
Prowadzone przez Shri Mataji Nirmala Devi 1987.05.05, Australia
First of all, please put your right hand on your heart.
Najpierw, połóżcie proszę prawą dłoń na sercu.
All the time, the left hand is towards Me.
Lewą rękę kierujcie przez cały czas do Mnie.
Now. Here you have to say, in your heart,
A teraz, tutaj musicie powiedzieć w swoim sercu,
with all sincerity, you have to ask Me a question.
z całą szczerością, musicie zadać Mi pytanie.
You have to ask Me a question, “Mother, am I the Spirit?”.
Musicie zadać Mi pytanie: "Matko, czy jestem Duchem?"
If you want to call Me ‘Shri Mataji’ you can call that, or you can call Me ‘Mother’,
Jeśli chcecie nazywać Mnie Shri Mataji, możecie tak mówić, lub możecie nazywać Mnie Matką,
but whichever way you want to call, that’s not important.
ale to, jak będziecie Mnie nazywać, nie jest ważne.
You have to say, “Mother, am I the Spirit?”.
Musicie powiedzieć: "Matko, czy ja jestem Duchem?"
Ask the question three times in your heart.
Zadajcie to pytanie trzy razy w swoim sercu.
This is a very fundamental question. Like a computer you are asking Me a question.
Zadajecie Mi pytanie, tak jak komputerowi.
Now bring the right hand onto the left-hand side of your stomach, in the upper part.
Teraz połóżcie prawą rękę po lewej stronie żołądka, w górnej jego części.
Here press it. Now this is the centre of your mastery, your guidance,
Naciśnijcie tutaj. To jest centrum waszego mistrzostwa, waszego przewodnictwa,
your Guru Tattwa as they say. So ask a question, “Mother, am I my own master?”.
waszej zasady Guru, jak ją nazywamy. Więc zapytajcie "Matko, czy ja jestem swoim własnym mistrzem?"
This is a question to be asked three times, “Mother, am I my own master?”.
To pytanie zadajcie trzy razy.
Now, bring your right hand down below, in the lower part of the abdomen.
Teraz przenieście prawą rękę niżej, na dolną część brzucha.
Now this is the centre from which all the Divine work is done,
To jest centrum, z którego wykonywana jest cała Boska praca,
all the pure work is done.
cała żywa praca.
Now this centre is such that you have to ask Me that,
Przy tym centrum musicie Mnie poprosić:
“Mother, please, give me pure knowledge.”
"Matko, proszę, daj mi czystą wiedzę."
If you do not ask, I cannot force on you.
"Matko, proszę daj mi czystą wiedzę". Jeśli nie poprosicie, Ja nie mogę wymusić tego na was.
So to ask Me six times, because this centre has got six petals.
Poproście Mnie 6 razy, bo to centrum ma sześć płatków.
“Mother, please, give me pure knowledge.”
"Matko, proszę, daj mi czystą wiedzę."
This works out all the Divine plans.
To wypracuje wszystkie Boskie plany.
Six times you just ask.
Po prostu poproście sześć razy.
As a result of this asking, the Kundalini starts getting awakened.
W rezultacie tej prośby, Kundalini zaczyna się budzić.
Now to help the Kundalini to rise, you have to cooperate with her.
Teraz, aby pomóc Kundalini się wznieść, musicie z nią współpracować.
So please, put your right hand on the left-hand side,
Więc proszę, połóżcie prawą dłoń po lewej stronie,
in the upper part of your abdomen and press it,
w górnej części brzucha i naciśnijcie
on your – is the stomach.
na swój żołądek.
Now here you have to say with full confidence, to help the Kundalini to rise,
Tutaj musicie powiedzieć z pełnym przekonaniem, aby pomóc Kundalini się unieść:
“Mother, I am my own master.” This you have to say ten times.
“Mother, I am my own master.” This you have to say ten times. "Matko, jestem swoim własnym mistrzem". To musicie powiedzieć 10 razy.
These are the Ten Commandments which you have to say, that,
To jest 10 przykazań, które musicie powiedzieć,
“Mother, I am my own master.”
"Matko, ja jestem swoim własnym mistrzem".
Now - ten times with full confidence.
10 razy z pełnym przekonaniem.
Now, please raise your right hand to your heart.
Teraz proszę, przesuńcie prawą dłoń na serce.
Now, here you have to say, again with full confidence,
Tutaj musicie powiedzieć, znowu z pełnym przekonaniem:
“Mother, I am the Spirit.” This is the truth, you are the Spirit,
"Matko, ja jestem Duchem". To jest prawda, jesteście Duchem.
but you have to say with full confidence, “Mother, I am the Spirit.”
Ale musicie powiedzieć z pełnym przekonaniem: "Matko, ja jestem Duchem".
This you have to say twelve times.
Musicie to wypowiedzieć 12 razy.
Now, one has to know that God Almighty is the Ocean of Love.
Trzeba wiedzieć, że Bóg Wszechmogący jest Oceanem Miłości.
But above all, He’s the Ocean of Forgiveness.
Ale przede wszystkim, On jest Oceanem Przebaczenia.
So He forgives; whatever wrong you do He forgives.
Więc On wybacza; cokolwiek złego robicie, On wybacza.
So don’t feel guilty and put your right hand across,
Więc nie czujcie się winni i połóżcie swoją prawą rękę
on the left-hand side, in the corner which is made by your neck and your shoulder.
po lewej stronie, w miejscu, gdzie szyja łączy się z ramieniem.
Now here you have to say, again with full confidence, sixteen times,
Teraz musicie powiedzieć, znów z przekonaniem, 16 razy:
“Mother, I am not guilty.” Please say it,
"Matko, ja nie jestem winny". Proszę powiedzcie to:
“Mother, I am not guilty.” Sixteen times.
"Matko, nie jestem winny" - 16 razy.
“I’m not guilty at all.”
"Nie jestem niczemu winny."
Please say it.
Proszę, powiedzcie to.
Baba, very hot.
Bardzo gorące.
Now raise your hand across on your forehead.
Teraz połóżcie rękę na czole.
Now this is the centre of Christ
To jest centrum Chrystusa
and is a very important centre.
i jest to bardzo ważne centrum.
Here you have to say from your heart,
Tutaj musicie powiedzieć z serca:
“Mother, I forgive everyone.” Please say it from your heart.
"Matko, wybaczam wszystkim". Proszę, powiedzcie to z serca.
How many times is not the point. “Mother, I forgive everyone.”
Nieważne ile razy. "Matko, przebaczam wszystkim."
Now, some would say that is very difficult to forgive.
Wiecie, ktoś może powiedzieć, że trudno jest wybaczyć.
But it’s a myth that we do not forgive or we forgive.
Ale to mit, że my nie przebaczamy lub przebaczamy.
We do not do anything in both the cases.
W obu przypadkach, my nic nie robimy.
But if we don’t forgive, then we play into wrong hands.
Ale jeśli nie przebaczamy, to jesteśmy pod złym wpływem.
So please say from your heart, “Mother, I forgive everyone.”
Więc proszę, powiedzcie to z serca: "Matko, przebaczam wszystkim".
Now please take your hand on the Back Agnya, the same centre
Teraz proszę, połóżcie rękę na tylnej Agnyi, to samo centrum
on the backside of your head, and allow your head to rest on it
z tyłu głowy i pozwólcie swojej głowie na niej spoczywać,
and push it back a little bit.
odchylcie głowę nieco do tyłu.
Now here you have to say -
Tutaj musicie powiedzieć,
for your satisfaction because you always feel guilty - that,
dla swojej satysfakcji, bo wy zawsze czujecie sie winni.
“Oh, Divine, if I have done anything wrong, please forgive me.”
"O Boskości, jeśli uczyniłem cokolwiek złego, proszę przebacz mi."
“Please, forgive me.”
"Proszę, przebacz mi."
From your heart.
Z całego serca.
Now to the fontanel bone area, where they say they give baptism,
Teraz na obszar ciemiączka, gdzie mówią, że dają chrzest,
but actually it’s an artificial one.
ale w rzeczywistości jest on sztuczny.
Stretch your hand fully and put your centre of your palm on top
Napnijcie dłoń i połóżcie jej środek
of the fontanel bone area, which was a very soft bone in your childhood.
na ciemiączku, które było bardzo miękkie w dzieciństwie.
Press it hard, press hard your scalp.
Naciśnijcie mocno, naciśnijcie mocno na skórę głowy.
Now you have to move it seven times, saying one thing,
Teraz musicie poruszać nią 7 razy mówiąc…
which you have to ask for, “Mother, please, give us my Self-realization.”
musicie o to poprosić: "Matko, proszę, daj mi moją Samorealizację".
Because I cannot force on you, so you’ve to ask for it.
Bo nie mogę wymusić tego na was, więc musicie o to poprosić.
Seven times, press it hard and move it seven times. Very hard.
7 razy, naciśnijcie mocno i poruszajcie 7 razy, bardzo mocno.
Slowly. Saying that.
Powoli, mówiąc to.
It’s good.
Jest dobrze.
Now, remove the right hand.
Teraz zdejmijcie prawą rękę.
Slowly open your eyes.
Powoli otwórzcie oczy.
Put your right hand towards Me and see on your left-hand.
Skierujcie prawą rękę do Mnie i sprawdźcie lewą ręką.
Raise it a little higher than your head
Podnieście trochę wyżej nad głową
and see if there’s the cool breeze is coming out of your head.
i sprawdźcie czy jest chłodny powiew wydobywający się z waszej głowy.
Some people might get it. Put the right hand towards Me please,
Niektórzy mogą to otrzymać. Połóżcie prawą rękę w moim kierunku proszę,
right hand towards Me. And with the left hand -
prawa ręka w moim kierunku. A lewą ręką
right hand towards Me - with the left hand.
- prawa ręka w moim kierunku - lewą ręką.
Just see if there’s a cool breeze coming out of your head.
Tylko sprawdźcie, czy z waszej głowy wychodzi chłodny powiew.
Now turn it, put left hand towards Me. See with your right hand.
Teraz na odwrót. Skierujcie lewą rękę do Mnie. Sprawdźcie prawą ręką.
Some people might get hot breeze. It’s alright.
Niektórzy mogą poczuć ciepły powiew. Ale to jest w porządku.
But after some time it will become cool.
A za jakiś czas stanie się chłodny.